The radiance of the night shines through my window
but the path to immortality is long.
The Eight Views and Nine-Bend Streams are desolate.
Living beings question the miseries of the world over a jar of wine.
Forget about Nirvana and rebirth,
I will break through the waves with my own flesh and blood.
The heavens are vast, so what if I was born mediocre ?
I stare at the Dao in my moments of madness
as the storm rages just below.
I've been thinking about life and death in my dreams.
I've unsheathed my sword to ask the immortals
why the world is a-changing.
Heaven and earth reveals its poignant truths.
Swallow the Four Seas and the Eight Wastelands,
experience all the vicissitudes of life in an instant.
I will defy the light in the sky
to continue to write a new chapter for all things in the three realms of existence.
Just a thought separates mortal from immortal.
Transform your insignificant body into light.
The hardships of the journey
will temper this young man's heart.
If I become a Renegade Immortal, will I hesitate to fight the heavens ?
Renegade Immortal
Subtitles by Bonobosubs
https://discord.gg/Ceckd4pdVA
Senior Sister,
Senior Brother Qian Mu forbade us from following him.
When he comes out and sees all this,
do you think he will scold us
for acting without his permission ?
We just built a residence near his cave,
it's nothing serious.
Besides,
cultivators like good environments.
We made this place this beautiful,
he won’t get angry.
Junior Sister Liu Wei,
you can relax.
After we spread rumors of Senior Brother Qian Mu,
I’ve collected a year's worth of souls in just a few months.
However...
Senior Sister,
visitors are getting more frequent.
If Senior Brother Qian Mu finds out
we’ve been using his reputation to collect souls,
he won’t forgive us !
I don't think so...
Junior Brother Qian Mu,
Guo Dongjian
Soul Refining Sect Inner disciple
Early stage Nascent Soul
I am Guo Dongjian.
I hope we can talk.
Nascent Soul cultivation !
Damn it,
we're in big trouble !
Go !
A Thousand-Soul Flag illusion ?
Thousand-Soul Flag
I also have
a Thousand-Soul Flag !
Surrender your Soul Flag
and I’ll let you leave.
If you can defeat me,
I’ll hand it over.
Senior Brother, be careful !
Vortex !
Among the Soul Refining Mountain disciples
only 2 have mastered the Soul Vortex...
How is this possible ?
3 months ago
Is this...
This beast is stronger than me,
I shouldn't act recklessly.
For now, I must focus on using the Spirit Vein to cultivate
and restore my Origin Soul.
Now that my cultivation is at Peak Nascent Soul,
it might be worth
studying Soul Flag spells.
The 3 Soul Refining Mountain spells are
Condense,
Soul Vortex
and Blood Sacrifice.
Condense
is the foundation of Soul Refining.
It shapes ethereal souls
into tangible forms
and puts them
inside a Soul Flag.
The Soul Vortex spell
is very rare.
Only at Nascent Soul
can one try to master it.
Vortex
Once the Soul Vortex is activated
it can rapidly absorb large amounts of souls.
Whether it is used for fighting or stealing souls
it is extremely powerful.
Congratulations, Senior Brother Qian Mu, on mastering the Soul Vortex...
Junior offers this Thousand-Soul Flag as a gift.
This Junior
will take his leave.
Wait.
Do you know who in the Soul Extracting Mountain has the jade slip ?
Su Jinshi of the Soul Extracting Mountain,
you can trade with him.
I congratulate Brother Qian Mu
on recovering most of his cultivation.
Liu Mei,
what are you here for ?
Don't make things up.
Wang Lin,
you’re in grave danger.
You must leave.
Leave planet Suzaku.
You don't know
but Red Butterfly was killed by my Senior Brother.
It looks like my duel with Red Butterfly
was merely a dogfight for certain people...
Leave,
the sooner, the better.
I’m doing this for you.
Liu Mei appears kind
but I keep having this weird feeling about her...
The weak expressions of these two...
Senior Brother, be careful !
Now I understand...
Liu Mei is showing all those emotions
to keep her true ruthless nature
hidden deep in her heart.
Liu Mei didn’t attack me while my cultivation was weak.
Her goal isn't killing me
but she definitely doesn’t have any good intentions.
Since you two helped me see Liu Mei’s true nature,
I’ll spare your lives.
The most urgent matter now
is mending my Origin Soul.
If I absorb more energy
and increase the pressure,
it will further compress my Origin Soul
and speed up my recovery.
Wang Lin's avatar
Early stage Soul Formation
I am back at Soul Formation
but my Origin Soul's healing has stopped.
Mending my Origin Soul
will require stronger spiritual energy pressure.
Damn animal !
The Ancestor has decreed that
the 3 Soul Flags beneath the 3 mountains
Ten Thousand-Soul Flag
belong whoever who can refine them.
After my last failure,
I spent decades preparing.
This time
you will surely be mine !
Blood Sacrifice !
Blood Sacrifice,
the last of the 3 Soul Refining spells.
It can multiply the Soul Flag’s power
by several times.
There's one more ?
Finally, you're out.
Soul Sealing Bell
I lost last time to this second primary soul.
This time, I’ll capture you !
It's working !
How come there's a third primary soul !?
Could there be
a fourth one ?
Enough,
I’ll return later.
It's weird,
a single Soul Flag can’t have so many primary souls.
There is only one possibility,
they’re all secondary souls.
I must keep taunting the secondary souls
to force the primary soul out.
Subduing this Soul Flag
is worth a try !
Is this
a Qilin soul fragment ?
This Qilin soul fragment
even if it's weaker than Ling Tianhou’s living Qilin,
has a memory inheritance
and can cast spells.
Its power
is comparable to Peak Late stage Soul Formation.
Vortex !
Let’s see
how long your soul energy can last !
Damn animal !
God Slaying Chariot,
activate !
If you were at full strength
you wouldn’t fear a beast soul.
But now,
you’re just a soul fragment.
Hundred Thousand-Soul Flag
A Hundred Thousand-Soul Flag !?
Rise !
Qilin primary soul,
return !
The energy fluctuations
didn’t attract the attention of the Soul Refining Sect’s Soul Formation Elders.
The top priority now
is to gather the 3 jade slips of spells for the Soul Flag.
Su Jinshi
Soul Refining Sect Inner disciple
A Soul Refining Mountain disciple ?
Hand over the Soul Extracting jade slip.
I can’t see through his cultivation...
I can give you the Soul Extracting jade slip
but I have a Soul Flag
that is still missing 300 souls fragments
to become a Thousand-Soul Flag.
If you can give me 300 souls,
I’ll give it to you.
Senior Brother is decisive,
how should I address you ?
Qian Mu.
So it’s Senior Brother Qian Mu.
Soul Extracting jade
This jade slip
records how to extract souls
and
the method to prevent them from dissipating.
Senior Brother Qian Mu,
do you plan to get the Soul Sealing jade next ?
Senior Brother, don’t bother.
The Soul Sealing jade slip
is only accessible to Soul Formation Elders.
Ordinary disciples
only use Soul Refining and Extracting.
The final Soul Flag spell
is only for Soul Formation Elders ?
My Origin Soul’s recovery
requires even greater pressure.
In that case,
why not.
Elders of the Soul Refining Sect,
come out and fight me !
To let go of the consequences of my actions
is to ignore the law of cause and effect
like scattered ink.
As destiny falls
in exchange for this moment of tainted dreams.
It makes the mountains lose their colors,
wither and melt into rivers.
Who can deceive
the law of the heavens ?
Countless generations
have tried before me.
But how could I not catch my dreams
within my warm fingers ?
You're at my side when I'm alone
giving me the strength to fight the will of the heavens.
Fortunately, my mind was open and honest.
I'm sorry we never got to see the fireworks
in the streets.
Can I break the vortex of our destiny ?
Can I break the rules ?
To run towards you !
I will fight the law of the heavens and the law of cause and effect
to cut down this tribulation with my own hands
and break through the reincarnation cycle.
All of that for the stars in your eyes.
I wish to bend this dream for the fire in my heart.
If your soul is willing to wander,
can I still take your hands
and hold them tight ?
I will defy the heavens and prevent the stars from falling.
I will overthrow the Immortals and the Demons in my heart.
I dream of destroying
the shackles of our fate.
You're the only one that can ignore the law of cause and effect.
You're the hardest to let go of.
I want to be with you again
so I can look in your eyes.
Even for a moment, it's worth it.